A Guide to the Stone Typographical Collection 1935(1947)1951
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Stone Typographical Collection 1935(1947)1951
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
382-e
This collection consists of 18 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This material was originally given to the Library by K.S. Giniger and Stringfellow Barr.
Scope and Content Information
This collection of 18 items, 1935(1947)1951, consists of galley proofs and book club proofs of books by various authors.
Contents List
- Galley Proof Jobs for Women over Thirty-Five by Julietta K. Arthur 1947, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Page Proof Mazzini, Portrait of an Exile by Stringfellow Barr 1935 (Box 1)
- Galley Proof Championship Football by Dana Xenophon Bible 1947 (Box 1)
- Galley Proof The Florida of the Inca by the Inca Garcilaso de la Vega, translated by John and Jeanette Varner 1951, 4 folders (Box 2)
- Book Club Proof Whirlpool by James Leal Henderson 1947 (Box 2)
- Galley Proof Whirlpool by James Leal Henderson 1947 (Box 2)
- Galley Proof Halfway to Heaven by Jean Hersey 1947 (Box 3)
- Galley Proof The 1-2-3 of Homemaking by Marion Hurst 1947 (Box 3)
- Book Club Proof Pamela Foxe by Dorothea Malm 1947 (Box 3)
- Galley Proof The Story of Hypnotism by Robert W. Marks 1947 (Box 3)
- Galley Proof The Conquest of the West by Walter Flavius McCaleb 1947, 3 copies (Box 3)
- Book Club Proof The Condemned by Jo Pagano 1947 (Box 4)
- Galley Proof The Condemned by Jo Pagano 1947 (Box 4)
- Book Club Proof Money Makes the Mare Go by Walter Steigleman 1947 (Box 4)
- Galley Proof The Condemned by Walter Steigleman 1947 (Box 4)
- Galley Proof Murder by Gaslight by Edward Wagenknecht 1947, 3 folders (Box 4)